{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
      "choices": [
        "Object-Oriented",
        "Object-Based",
        "Procedural",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "type": "MCQs",
      "correctAnswer": "Object-Oriented"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
      "choices": [
        "stringify()",
        "parse()",
        "convert()",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "type": "MCQs",
      "correctAnswer": "stringify()"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
      "choices": [
        "var",
        "let",
        "var and let",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "type": "MCQs",
      "correctAnswer": "var and let"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
      "choices": [
        "document.write()",
        "console.log()",
        "window.alert",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "type": "MCQs",
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
      "choices": [
        "const",
        "var",
        "let",
        "constant"
      ],
      "type": "MCQs",
      "correctAnswer": "const"
    }
  ],
  "results": [
    {
      "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
      "answer": "Object-Oriented",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": "0m:35s:38ms",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
      "answer": "stringify()",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": "0m:15s:23ms",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
      "answer": "var",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": "0m:13s:27ms",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
      "answer": "document.write()",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": "0m:16s:42ms",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
      "answer": "var",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": "0m:13s:54ms",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
      "answer": "Object-Oriented",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": "0m:47s:37ms",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
      "answer": "parse()",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": "0m:15s:2ms",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
      "answer": "var and let",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": "0m:14s:32ms",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
      "answer": "window.alert",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": "0m:15s:19ms",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
      "answer": "const",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": "0m:18s:35ms",
      "id": 15
    }
  ]
}